<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui="urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder"
    xmlns:g="urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui"
    xmlns:cm="urn:import:hotmath.gwt.cm_mobile_shared.client.ui">

    <ui:style>
       .main {
           font-size: 1.1em;
           background: white;
           padding: 10px;
       }
       
       .main li {
           margin-bottom: 15px;
       }
    </ui:style>

    <g:HTMLPanel styleName="{style.main}">
            <p>
                We include web resources within student lessons via their Web Links
                resource menu.
            </p>
            
            <p>
                The Our School tab shows links for your account. Links may be
                correlated with specific lessons and assigned to specific groups. To
                see details or make a change, select the link and use View/Edit.
            </p>
        
            <p>
               The All Schools tab shows links that are used for all accounts.
            </p>
        
            <p>
               For more information, please see our Training Videos.
            </p>
        
               
           <ul>
              <li>
                  <b>Tip-1</b>: To restrict an All Schools link, Copy the link from the All
                  Schools tab and then make changes in the Our School tab. The version
                  of the link in Our School takes precedence. To disable the entire All
                  Schools links, use Mange Groups > Group Settings.
              </li>
        
              <li><b>Tip-2</b>: When creating a link, there are two ways to display it for
                  students. One may work better than the other. If you choose the
                  "Alternate" method, the link will open for students in a new browser
                  window rather than be shown centered within Catchup Math. If a
                  particular link behaves poorly, set the New Window checkbox in
                  Options.
              </li>
        
              <li><b>Tip-3</b>: You can turn an Our School link on and off in real time using
                 the Offline selection in View/Edit > Options. You might use this to
                 allow games as a reward at the end of a class period.
              </li>
        
              <li>
                 <b>Tip-4</b>: For some commonly used links such as Khan Academy and YouTube,
                  we make a link conversions automatically for optimal display.
              </li>    
        
              <li>
                 <b>Tip-5</b>: Let us know at support@hotmath.com if you have suggestions!
              </li>
                 
           </ul>

</g:HTMLPanel>
    
</ui:UiBinder> 